http://www.sleightadvertising.com/privacy-policy/

X
Why Choose SleightMeet The TeamBlogCase StudiesTestimonialsCareers
Portfolio
Back
X
Brand DevelopmentDigital MarketingSocial MediaVideo ProductionWebsite Design
X
Digital MarketingWebsite DesignBrand DevelopmentVideo ProductionMedia BuyingSocial Media
X
Google AdsGoogle ShoppingBing AdvertisingYouTube AdvertisingGeotargeting
X
Brand DevelopmentAssessment & StrategyTarget Market ResearchCompetitive AnalysisLogo Design
X
Aerial VideoCompany VideoMotion GraphicsSocial Media VideoTestimonial VideoVideo Blogs
Still Photography
Back
X
Aerial PhotographyFood PhotographyHeadshotsOnline PhotographyProduct Photography
Production Studio
Non-Profit Video
Back
X
Event VideoFundraising VideoOnline VideoOrganization VideoTestimonial Video
Sleight Advertising Privacy Policy
Sleight Advertising is committed to keeping any and all personal information collected from those individuals that visit our website and make use of our online facilities and services accurate, confidential, secure and private. Our privacy policy has been designed and created to ensure those affiliated with Sleight Advertising of our commitment and realization of our obligation not only to meet but to exceed most existing privacy standards. Therefore, this privacy policy agreement shall apply to Sleight Advertising, and thus it shall govern any and all data collection and usage thereof. Through the use of https://www.sleightadvertising.com/ you are herein consenting the following data procedures expressed within this agreement.Collection of Information
This website collects various types of information, such as:
> Information automatically collected when visiting our website, which may include cookies, third party tracking technologies and server logs.
We may also gather information about the type of browser you are using, IP address or type of operating system to assist us in providing and maintaining superior quality service.
It is highly recommended and suggested you review the privacy policies and statements of any website you choose to use or frequent as a mean to better understand the way in which other websites garner, make use of and share information.Use of Information Collected
Sleight Advertising may collect and make use of personal information to assist in the operation of our website to ensure delivery of the services you need and request. At the time, we may find it necessary to use personally identifiable information as a means to keep you informed of other possible products and/or services they may be available to you from https://www.sleightadvertising.com/ . Sleight Advertising may also be in contact with you in regards to completing serves and/or research questionnaires related to your opinion of current or potential future services that may be offered.
Sleight Advertising does not now, nor in the futures, sell, rent or lease any of our customer lists and/or names to any third parties.
Sleight Advertising may deem it necessary to follow websites and/or pages that users may frequent in an effort to glean what types of services and/or products may be popular to customers or the general public.
Sleight Advertising may disclose your personal information, without prior notice to you, only if required to do so in accordance with applicable laws and/or in a good faith belief that such action is deemed necessary or is required in an effort to:
> Remain in conformance with any decrees, laws and/or statutes or in an effort to comply with any process which may be served upon Sleight Advertising and/or our website;
> Maintain, safeguard and/or preserve all the rights and/or property of Sleight Advertising; and
> Perform under demanding conditions in an effort to safeguard the personal safety of users of https://www.sleightadvertising.com/ and/or the general public.Children Under Age of 13
Sleight Advertising does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of 13 without verifiable parental consent. If it is determined that such information has been inadvertently collected by anyone under the age of 13, we shall immediately take necessary steps to ensure that such information is deleted from our system’s database. Anyone under the age of 13 must seek parent or guardian permission to use this website.Links to Other Websites
Our website does contain links to affiliate and other websites. Sleight Advertising does not claim nor accept responsibility for any privacy policies, practices and/or procedures of other such websites. Therefore, we encourage all users and visitors to be aware when they leave our website and to read privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. The aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement applies only and sole to the information collected by our website.Security
Sleight Advertising shall endeavor and shall take every precaution to maintain adequate physical, procedural and technical security with respects to our offices and information storages facilities so as to prevent any loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of the user’s personal information under our control. Sleight Advertising reserves the right to update and/or change the terms of our privacy policy, and as such we will post those changes to our website, so that our users and visitors are always aware of the type of information that we collect, how it will be used, and under what circumstances, if any, we may disclose such information.Acceptance of Terms
Through the use of this website, you are hereby accepting the terms and conditions stipulated within the aforementioned Privacy Policy Agreement. If you are not in agreement with our terms and conditions, you should refrain from further use of our sites. In addition, your continued use of our website following the posting of any updates or changes to our terms and conditions shall mean that you are in agreement and acceptance of such changes.Sleight Advertising
(402) 334-3530
15405 Weir St. Omaha, NE 68137
RECENT WORKSIllustra Dermatology
| Mobile First WebsiteWebsite DesignCLS
| Mobile First WebsiteWebsite DesignMidAmerica Basement Systems | Mobile First WebsiteWebsite DesignVIEW PORTFOLIO
